<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android News App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="recent_news">RECENT NEWS</string>
    <string name="category">CATEGORY</string>

    <!--__________________________-->

    <string name="news_1_title">
        Amazon’s gadget battle with Google could upend its Alexa allies
    </string>
    <string name="news_1_date">
        12.04.18
    </string>
    <string name="news_1_text">
        TP-Link has been enjoying a very good run on Amazon.com. Two of the companys Alexa-enabled smart plugs have dominated Amazons electric
        plugs best-seller list for most of this year, helping the Chinese manufacturer sell thousands of plugs.
        Unfortunately for TP-Link, its about to get fresh competition from Amazon itself. The e-commerce giant last month held a product launch event in Seattle,
        where it unveiled a long list of new devices including the Alexa-enabled Amazon Smart Plug. The plug goes on sale for $25 next week, a few bucks more than TP-Links plugs.
    </string>
    <!--<string name="news_1_image_src">

    </string>-->

    <!--__________________________-->

    <string name="news_2_title">
        Gareth Southgate says Joe Hart could still earn England recall
    </string>
    <string name="news_2_date">
        04.10.18
    </string>
    <string name="news_2_text">
        There was no space for Burnley keeper Hart in Southgate 25-man squad for the upcoming matches against Croatia and Spain in the UEFA Nations League.
        Instead, Southgate selected uncapped duo Marcus Bettinelli and Alex McCarthy along with Jack Butland and Jordan Pickford as his goalkeeping options.
        A series of impressive displays for the Clarets has seen Hart keep his place in goal ahead of fellow club team-mates Tom Heaton and Nick Pope.
    </string>
    <!--<string name="news_2_image_src">

    </string>-->

    <!--__________________________-->

    <string name="news_3_title">
        Here come Wi-Fi 4, 5 and 6 in plan to simplify 802.11 networking names
    </string>
    <string name="news_3_date">
        05.10.18
    </string>
    <string name="news_3_text">
        The idea is to be clearer about whats better and what your phone or home router can handle without sounding as much like an electronic engineer.
        Not that theres anything wrong with electronic engineers, but even techies can have a hard time remembering that IEEE 802.11 means wireless networks,
        IEEE 1394 governs FireWire data connections, and IEEE 802.3 is about Ethernet network connections.
        The underlying Wi-Fi specifications will keep their IEEE technical names, of course. The Wi-Fi Alliance comes later in the development process,
        just before the point when consumers get involved, smoothing the way with compatibility tests that let device manufacturers put reassuring certification
        logos on their product boxes.
    </string>
    <!--<string name="news_3_image_src">

    </string>-->
    <!--__________________________-->

    <string name="news_4_title">
        Uber joins Lyft in offering rides to voters for the midterm elections
    </string>
    <string name="news_4_date">
        15.08.18
    </string>
    <string name="news_4_text">
        The ride-hailing company announced Thursday that its offering free rides to the polls for those people who say transportation barriers are why they vote.
        It also created a polling place button to help voters more easily find where they need to go to cast their ballot on Tuesday, Nov. 6.
        "With the 2018 elections around the corner, many organizations and companies across the country are going the extra mile to support our democratic process,"
        Uber CEO Dara Khosrowshahi wrote in a blog post. "Using our technology and resources, we can help make it easier for every Uber rider in the US to get to 
        their polling place at the push of a button.
    </string>
    <!--<string name="news_4_image_src">

    </string>-->
    
</resources>
